{
  "sessions": [],
  "todos": [],
  "reminders": [],
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "a",
      "description": "b",
      "created_at": "2025-05-25 12:52:58",
      "cards": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "a",
          "back": "b",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "zor",
          "back": "zor",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "kolay",
          "back": "1",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "z2",
          "back": "a",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "z3",
          "back": "b",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "k2",
          "back": "a",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "k3",
          "back": "b",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "m2",
          "back": "m",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "m1",
          "back": "a",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "deck_id": 1,
          "front": "m",
          "back": "a",
          "tags": [],
          "created_at": "2025-05-25",
          "reviews": [],
          "current_interval": 1,
          "current_ease_factor": 2.5,
          "due_date": "2025-05-25",
          "is_new": true
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "next_deck_id": 0
}